Say, "Neighbour, acknowledge God for what He has done".
Come on, put your hands together for Jesus.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Somebody bless the name of the Lord.
Come on, clap!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Acknowledge God for what He has done
He will do it again
Come on, bless the name of the Lord.
Clap.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Acknowledge God for what He has done
He will do it again.
Sing: Acknowledge God!
Acknowledge God for what He has done
He will do it again
Sing: Acknowledge God.
Acknowledge God for what He has done
He will do it again
Come on, bless the name of the Lord!
The SCOAN Sunday Service.
Are you happy?
Acknowledge God for the role He's been playing
He will do it again
Sing: Acknowledge God.
Acknowledge God for the role He's been playing
He will do it again
Say: Acknowledge God.
Acknowledge God for the role He's been playing
He will do it again
Somebody clap your hands.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Is somebody happy?
Cry no more
Acknowledge God, He will do it again
Complain no more
Sing: Cry no more.
Cry no more
Acknowledge God, He will do it again
Complain no more
Sing: Cry no more.
Cry no more
Acknowledge God, He will do it again
Complain no more
One more time sing: Cry no more.
Cry no more
Acknowledge God, He will do it again
Sing: Complain no more.
Complain no more
Acknowledge God, He will do it again
Faith has done it
God has done it
He is my Healer, your Healer, Defender, Provider
He is my Saviour, your Saviour, Deliverer, Defender
God has done it
Faith has done it
He is my Healer, your Healer, Defender, Provider
God has done it
He is your Saviour, my Saviour, Defender, Waymaker
He is my Healer, your Healer, Defender, Provider
God has done it
Faith has done it
Hallelujah
TT: Esther Mwelwa 12/23/18
RV: Mel Flowers 28/12/2018